citynews1130.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Rogers Media

### General Faqs

  * What is Rogers Media?
  * Where can I learn about the Rogers Group of Companies privacy policy?
  * What is the purpose of these privacy policy FAQs?
  * What is personal information?
  * Does Rogers collect personal information?
  * How does Rogers use information it gathers about me?
  * Might I be contacted by organizations outside Rogers?
  * What are marketing preferences?
  * How can I change my marketing preferences?
  * How can I change or update my e-mail newsletter subscriptions?
  * Does Rogers Media use telemarketing to sell magazine subscriptions?
  * What about personalized ads in magazines?
  * How does Rogers Media protect the privacy of children?
  * I’m registering on one of your websites for the first time, but my name is here already. How?
  * Do Rogers Media websites use cookies?
  * Do Rogers Media websites record information about my computer or my visit?
  * How does Rogers Media advertise on its website?
  * What about information on public forums?
  * What steps do you take for the security of my information?
  * How else can I protect my privacy online?
  * What happens to information I provide on a contest entry?
  * Are there other ways my information will be used?

Contact Us

#### What is Rogers Media?

Rogers Media Inc. operates Rogers Broadcasting and Rogers Publishing. Rogers Media Inc. is a wholly owned subsidiary of Rogers Communications Partnership (Rogers) (TSX: RCI; NYSE: RCI). Rogers Communications and its subsidiaries and affiliates are referred to as the Rogers Group of Companies.

#### Where can I learn about the Rogers Group of Companies privacy policy?

#### What is the purpose of these privacy policy FAQs?

These FAQs provide additional information regarding, and interpretation of, the Rogers Group of Companies’ privacy policy as it applies to Rogers Media. The FAQs explain how Rogers Media treats your personal information collected in connection with your subscription to all Rogers Media publications and your interactions with Rogers Media radio, website and digital properties. They also provide contact information in the event that you want to make further inquiries regarding your personal information.

#### What is personal information?

Personal information is any information that is related to an identifiable individual. It typically includes such information as your name, e-mail address, or mailing address. It could also include preferences you provided at websites or other information. It does not include the business contact information of a person, such as name, title and mailing contact information.

#### Does Rogers collect personal information?

We collect personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address, or other personal information when you register with a website or order a product or service. You may also be asked for personal information when you enter into contests or promotions sponsored by us or our partners.

#### How does Rogers use information it gathers about me?

Rogers Media uses your personal information to provide you with products or services that you have requested. We may further use such information to develop and customize products or services to better meet your needs and preferences, and to offer you products and services from Rogers, including any companies within the Rogers Group of Companies.

#### Might I be contacted by organizations outside Rogers?

Advertisers may ask Rogers Media for permission to send material to you that you may find of interest. In such cases, your name, email or mailing address are only released to a reputable third party service bureau for the purpose of sending the specific material. All such advertising material is reviewed by Rogers Media and subject to approval for acceptable advertising content.

If you would prefer that your name, email or mailing address not be provided to marketers outside of Rogers Group of Companies, please [click here](https://www.rogersmedia.com/contact/) for a list of Rogers Media properties and links to their respective customer account logins.

#### What are marketing preferences?

Your relationship with Rogers Media permits us to contact you about our products and services, as well as those of our affiliates in the Rogers Group of Companies. But if you prefer otherwise, we provide clear and easy ways for you to tell us so. These are your personal marketing preferences.

#### How can I change my marketing preferences?

To access and change your marketing preferences, please [click here](https://www.rogersmedia.com/contact/) for a list of Rogers Media properties and links to their respective customer account logins.

#### How can I change or update my e-mail newsletter subscriptions?

We have many e-mail newsletters for you to choose from and realize your preferences may change over time. To review or update your e-mail newsletter subscriptions please [click here](https://www.rogersmedia.com/contact/) for a list of Rogers Media properties and links to their respective customer account logins.

#### Does Rogers Media use telemarketing to sell magazine subscriptions?

Yes, some consumers find it convenient to be contacted by phone either to start new subscriptions or to renew an existing subscription. The authorized agents who sell new subscriptions are required to make use of the national “Do Not Call” registry to ensure that they do not call the phone numbers of people who have registered. If you are already a subscriber and do not want to receive telemarketing calls, you may add your phone number to our internal Do Not Call list by sending your request to:

For Consumer Publications – [webmedia@rci.rogers.com](mailto:webmedia@rci.rogers.com)  
For Business Publications – [bppgservice@rci.rogers.com](mailto:bppgservice@rci.rogers.com)

You can get more information about the national “Do Not Call” registry here <http://www.crtc.gc.ca/eng/INFO_SHT/t1031.htm>.

#### What about personalized ads in magazines?

Occasionally an advertiser may ask that we print the name of subscribers on their advertisement in our publications. When this is done, the subscriber’s name is printed on the ad at the same time that the mailing label is printed on the cover of the magazine. The subscriber’s name appears only in their personal copy of the magazine. If you would prefer not have your name included in such advertisements, please [click here](https://customer.rogersmagazineservice.com/app/) for a list of Rogers Media properties and links to their respective customer account logins.

Please note ‘Do Not Personalize’ is not applicable to business magazines.

#### How does Rogers Media protect the privacy of children?

The privacy of children is important to us. We will not knowingly send direct mailings, e-mail or other correspondence to anyone who indicates that they are younger than 16 years old. Your children should always ask you for permission before sending personal information to Rogers Media or to anyone else. Any personal information we gather about children under the age of 16 would be used solely for demographic purposes. Access to some of our websites may be prohibited to children under a certain age as specified in the website’s Terms of Service. Rogers Media cannot verify the validity of persons claiming to be age-eligible to access such websites.

#### I’m registering on one of your websites for the first time, but my name is here already. How?

Some Rogers Media websites may share online registration services. Any information you provide while registering for a website is tied to your e-mail address. If you use the same e-mail address to register at another Rogers Media website, the associated information will be retrieved, so you don’t have to re-enter it.

#### Do Rogers Media websites use cookies?

Yes, Rogers Media websites use cookies. A cookie is set when you register on our websites.

A cookie is a small text file sent to your internet browser’s files for our reference. No one else can read this file. Cookies allow our server computer to recognize your computer when you return to our websites, so you don’t have to re-register and so we can retain any preferences you may have given us. If you do not wish to receive cookies, most browsers allow you to be alerted when a cookie is sent to your computer, so you can decide whether to accept it.

#### Do Rogers Media websites record information about my computer or my visit?

Rogers Media collects IP addresses and related information for the purposes of system administration and to create aggregate statistical reports for advertisers. This information cannot identify you personally.

Browser information (i.e. the URL of the webpage you were just on, the IP address of the computer you are using, your domain type, and your browser version) is automatically recorded as part of transmitting information over the Internet.

We may use it to help us display information in the best format for you.

We may develop summary reports for advertisers, to help them better understand our audience and provide advertisements that are more likely to be of interest to you. For example, we may report total number of visitors to our website in general or to specific webpages, average length of visit, etc. No identifying data about individuals is reported.

During your visit to our websites, we may record choices you have made and use this to provide more customized content or advertising. The data does not identify you and is not retained after your visit. This is sometimes called “clickstream” data.

We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our websites and promotions, or we may allow our affiliates and third party service providers to use these devices on our behalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our websites, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a notice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behaviour on our websites, as well as give us a way to measure the effectiveness of our promotions and performance.

#### How does Rogers Media advertise on its website?

The ads appearing on many of the Rogers Media websites are delivered to you using online advertising networks, and Adobe Media Optimizer technology. Information about your visits to this website, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad or visited certain pages of Rogers Media websites (but not your name, address, email or other personal information) is used to serve ads to you.

The ad network providers use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of the advertisements served to you on Rogers Media websites or through affiliate advertising network providers.

Web beacons utilize JavaScript code and write information to cookies, which are small files on your computer. If you do not want a cookie to be written, simply change the setting in your browser. For more information and how to ‘opt-out’ from ad network providers’ cookies, visit the [Your Ad Choices website](http://youradchoices.ca/choices).

#### What about information on public forums?

Rogers Media websites may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### What steps do you take for the security of my information?

Our websites use industry-standard security measures to protect data against loss, misuse and interception by third parties. Our security policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary. However, Rogers Media assumes no liability for interception, alteration or misuse of information transmitted over the Internet.

#### How else can I protect my privacy online?

Generally speaking, whenever you disclose personal information online there is a risk that the information may be intercepted, collected and used. That goes for information disclosed on message boards, in chat areas – or even in e-mail. The Rogers Group of Companies is not responsible if that information is intercepted. You transmit information at your own risk.

Co-branded websites and third party websites and services may be accessible through Rogers Media websites. Third parties may collect information for their own contests or promotions, and may have their own privacy and data collection practices. The Rogers Group of Companies is not responsible for and bears no liability for these policies or actions.

You alone are responsible for keeping passwords and information safe. Be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.

#### What happens to information I provide on a contest entry?

Rogers Media uses a variety of contests and similar promotions to increase awareness of our products and services. We generally request contact information so that we can notify you if you are a prize winner. As well, in some cases we may contact contest entrants with product information. Contest entries generally include a way for you to indicate that you do not want to be contacted based on the information on your entry. Because contests may involve co-sponsors outside Rogers Group of Companies who have their own privacy practices, it is always advisable to read the entry form and contest rules before entering.

#### Are there other ways my information will be used?

Rogers Media may also use or disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under circumstances specifically described to you when we collect the information (such as in a Terms of Service or Use agreement).
